Paetel, Karl O.; Papers ger072
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Periodicals Collections, 1913-1978; 9
  - Exile and Other Periodicals, 1914-1975; 9.2
    - Der Weltkampf. Monatsschrift f. Weltpolitik, völkische Kultur u. die Judenfrage aller Länder – bound volume, heavily marked by Paetel VII, No. 73-84 (1930). (Box 71, Folder 3)
    - Wiking-Ruf. Mitteilungsblatt der ehemaligen europäischen Soldaten der Waffen-SS für Vermißten-Such- und Hilfsdienst, 1951-1958 (Box 71, Folder 4)
      I, No. 1-3 (1951); subtitle changed to Mitteilungsblatt der europäischen Soldaten der ehemaligen Waffen-SS für Vermißten-Such- und Hilfsdienst II, No. 4-9, 11-26 (1952-1953); III, No. 1-12 (1954); IV, No. 1-12 (1955); V, No. 1-12 (1956); VI, No. 1-12 (1957); VII, No. 1-3 (1958).
    - Bücher-Briefe – exile publication, 1950-1952 (Box 72, Folder 1)
      No. 1-4, 7, 8, 10 (1950-1951); II, No. 11 (1951); III, No. 13, 14 (1952).
    - Bulletin on German Questions, 1949-1954; 1957-1963 (Box 72, Folder 2)
      I, No. 10-15 (1949); II, No. 36/37-46 (1950-1951); III, No. 47-60/61, 64/65-68 (1951-1952); title changed to Bulletin on German Questions with Contemporary Archive IV, No. 69/70-77, 80-88, 90/91 (1952-1953); title changed to Bulletin on German Questions with Contemporary Archives V, No. 113, 119 (1954); VIII, No. 187/188 (1957); IX, No. 190-209, 211-212 (1957-1958); X, No. 213/214-235/236 (1958-1959); XI, No. 237/238-261 (1959-1960); XII, No. 262/263-284 (1960-1961); XIII, No. 285/286/287-289, 291-299, 302-306/307, 309 (1961-1962); XIV, No. 310-311, 315-320/321, 324/325-329/330, 332 (1962-1963).
    - Europe Speaks Germany 14 July; 27 August (1945); 1 issue (undated). (Box 72, Folder 3)
    - Die Hilfe. Wochenschrift für Politik, Literatur und Kunst – rare World War I publication, 1914-1919 (Box 72, Folder 4)
      No. 1-5 (1914); No. 6-17 (1915); No. 18-26, 28 (1916); No. 30-35, 37-41 (1917); No. 43-53 (1918); No. 54 (1919).
    - In Re: Germany, 1941-1944 (Box 72, Folder 5)
      I, No. 1-11 (1941); II, No. 1-12 (1942); III, No. 1-12 (1943); IV, No. 1-2/3 (1944).
    - P.E.N.-Club Deutscher Autoren im Ausland. Mitteilungen (London) - exile, 1949-1950; 1953-1976 (Box 73, Folder 1)
      No. 1-4, 8 (1949-1950); Nov. (1953); March, June, Sept. (1954); October (1955); title changed to P.E.N. Zentrum deutscher Autoren im Ausland. Mitteilungsblatt December (1956); Jan., August (1957); title changed to Bericht Sept., Nov. (1958); Jan., May, October (1959); February, July, Nov. (1960); May, Nov. (1961); May, Sept. (1962); April, August (1963); Jan., June, Sept., December (1964); April, Sept. (1965); Jan., April, August (1966); Jan., June (1967); February, July (1968); Jan. (1969); February, July (1970); May, October (1971); Jan., May (1972); Jan., May, Sept. (1973); February, June, October (1974); February, August (1975); Jan., May (1976).
    - Politische Briefe – exile publication, edited by Pablo Hesslein (some photocopies), 1944-1952 (Box 73, Folder 2)
      No. 11 (1944); No. 12-14, Sonderausgabe, 17-23 (1945); No. 24-29, 32-35 (1946); IV, No. 36 (1947); V, No. 54 (1948); VI, No. 60/61-70 (1949); VII, No. 72/73, 76-83 (1950); VIII, No. 84-95 (1951); IX, No. 96-100 (1952).
    - Der Ruf. Zeitschrift der deutschen Kriegsgefangenen in USA, 1945 March 1; 1945 May 15-1946 May 1 (Box 73, Folder 3)
      No. 1 (March 1, 1945); No. 5-26 (May 15, 1945-May 1, 1946); 2 special supplements.
    - Wiener Library Bulletin, 1946-1947; 1949-1965; 1974 (Box 73, Folder 4)
      I, No. 2 (1946/1947); III, No. 2-6 (1949); IV, No. 1, 5-6 (1950); V, No. 1-6 (1951); VI, No. 1-6 (1952); VII, No. 1-6 (1953); VIII, No. 1-6 (1954); IX, No. 1-6 (1955); X, No. 1-6 (1956); XI, No. 1-6 (1957); XII, No. 1-6 (1958); XIII, No. 1-6 (1959); XIV, No. 1-3 (1960); XV, No. 1-2 (1961); XVI, No. 1-4 (1962); XVII, No. 1-4 (1963); XVIII, No. 1-4 (1964); XIX, No. 1-3 (1965); XXVII, N. S. No. 32 (1974).
    - Wirtschaftliche Privatinformationen fuer Chile und Suedamerika. Unabhaengige Privatpublikation – edited by Pablo Hesslein, 1949-1953 (Box 73, Folder 5)
      XI, No. 116/117-119, 123-125 (1949); XII, No. 133/134, 137-139 (1950); XIII, No. 140-148/149, 151 (1951); XIV, No. 152-155 (1952); XV, No. 1, 3, 5, 6 (1953).
    - Wort und Tat. Internationale Monatsschrift – exile No. 1-7 (1946-1947). (Box 73, Folder 6)
    - Die Zeitungsschau. Ausgabe "Politik" – postwar Germany II, No. 100 (1947). (Box 73, Folder 7)
    - Die Zeitungsschau. Ausgabe "Wirtschaft" – postwar Germany II, No. 11-25 (1947). (Box 73, Folder 8)
    - Miscellaneous magazine issues, heavily marked by Paetel, Undated (Box 73, Folder 9)
- Karl O. Paetel Bibliography, ca. 2006